creativeboom.co.uk 2019-03-30

# Terms & Conditions | Creative Industries | Creative Boom

This site is owned and operated by Creative Boom Limited (“Creative Boom”, “we” or “us”). These terms and conditions govern your use of the creativeboom.com website (our “Site”), including but not limited to, the Creative Boom Jobs Board, and govern your relationship with Creative Boom.

All activities and actions performed on our Site are subject to these terms and conditions. All users, both unregistered visitors and members, are subject to these terms and conditions. By using or contributing to or registering with our Site you enter into a binding contract with us on the following terms and conditions. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, you should not use our Site.

## Registering with and accessing the Site

You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself when registering with the Site and agree to maintain and promptly update your registration data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any username and/or password provided to you. You agree to be responsible for any unauthorised use resulting from a failure on your part to maintain the confidentiality of any username and/or password provided to you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorised use of your registration or password.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to suspend or terminate your registration and to deny access to our Site or any part of our Site at any time and for any reason whatsoever without notice.

## User submissions

You understand that you are responsible for all data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages or other materials (“Content”), communicated by you whether publicly posted or privately transmitted. Under no circumstances will we be liable in any way for any Content, including (without limitation) any errors or omissions in any Content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of your use of any Content. You agree that you must evaluate and bear all risks associated with the use of any Content including any reliance on its accuracy or completeness.

You agree not to:

  * Upload, post, email or submit any Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libellous, invasive of another’s privacy, hateful, embarrassing to another person or entity or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;
  * Upload, post, email or submit Content that infringes any intellectual property rights of others or that reveals trade secrets or that infringes the publicity rights of others without first obtaining their permission;
  * Upload, post, email or submit any Content that you do not have a right to transmit under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships;
  * Upload, post, email or submit sexually explicit Content or Content that harms or may harm minors in any way;
  * Upload, post, email or submit Content which is inaccurate or misleading;
  * Impersonate another person or entity, falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity or disguise the origin of any Content;
  * Collect or store personal data about other users;
  * Upload, post, email or submit Content that contains computer viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software, hardware or telecommunications equipment;
  * Violate any applicable national or international laws or regulations.

We reserve the right in our sole discretion to remove or refuse to publish any Content for any reason whatsoever at any time and without notice.

You agree to indemnify and hold us and our subsidiaries, affiliates, employees, officers, agents or partners harmless from and against any direct or indirect loss or damage (including consequential loss and loss of profits, goodwill or business opportunities arising from any third party claim in relation to any Content you upload, post or email or submit on or through our Site, or arising from any breach by you of these Terms and Conditions.

## Copyright

All rights in the design, text, graphics, and other material on our Site and the selection or arrangement thereof are the copyright of us or other third parties.

As a user, you may view, print and download the material for your own personal use only (but not in a systematic or regular manner so as to create a database of the contents).

You agree not to reproduce the material or transmit it to or store it in any other website or disseminate it in any other form.

You agree not to sell or modify the material or reproduce, display, publicly perform, distribute, or otherwise use the material in any way for any public or commercial purpose without the express written permission of the copyright owner.

You grant to us a worldwide, royalty-free, irrevocable, non-exclusive licence (including the right to sub-licence) to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform and display any Content (in whole or in part) you upload, post or submit and/or to incorporate such Content in other works in any form, media or technology.

From time to time we may in our sole discretion permit users to use the “Creative Boom” and/or “CB” name and/or logo on other websites, including but not limited to, social networking sites (“Third Party Sites”). If you wish to use the Creative Boom and/or CB name and/or logo you must obtain written permission from a director of Creative Boom. Where such permission is granted we reserve the right in our sole discretion to withdraw such permission for any reason whatsoever and at any time. You agree to immediately remove the Creative Boom and/or CB name and/or logo from any Third Party Sites in the event that our permission is withdrawn and agree not to do anything which would or may harm the Creative Boom brand or the goodwill of Creative Boom.

## Advertising and sponsorship

Advertisers and sponsors agree to ensure that material submitted for inclusion on our Site complies with any applicable national or international laws or regulations or codes. We do not accept responsibility for any errors or inaccuracies contained in advertising and sponsorship material.

We reserve the right in our sole discretion to remove or refuse to publish any advertisement for any reason whatsoever at any time and without notice.

## Privacy policy

You agree that we may collect, store, and use information about you in accordance with our privacy policy. You acknowledge and agree to be bound by the terms of our privacy policy.

## Exclusions and limitations

We do not provide materials on the Site for any specific purposes or persons. Accordingly, it is not intended to be relied upon in making any particular decisions and appropriate independent advice should be obtained before doing so.

We do not represent or warrant that:

  * access to our Site or any part of it will be uninterrupted, reliable or fault free;
  * our Site or any of its contents will be accurate, complete, reliable, true or suitable for any purpose;
  * we endorse any opinions expressed by users of the Site; or
  * any services (whether or not provided by us) will be provided with due care and skill.

To the extent permitted by law, we exclude all liability (whether arising in contract, tort or otherwise and whether or not due to our negligence) which we may otherwise have to you as a result of:

  * any technical, factual, textual or typographical inaccuracies, errors or omissions on or relating to our Site or any information on our Site;
  * the unavailability of our Site (or any part of it) or services;
  * any delay in providing, or failure to provide or make available services or any negligent provision of services;
  * any misrepresentation on or relating to our Site or any services.

You agree that we shall have no liability for indirect or consequential losses, loss of data, income or profits or damages for loss of or damage to property.

You agree that each of these limitations and exclusions is reasonable having regard to the nature of our Site.

None of the exclusions or limitations shall exclude or restrict our liability for death or personal injury caused by our negligence or shall affect any statutory rights which are not capable of being excluded. However, in such case, our obligation, where permitted by law, will be limited to the re-supply of our site or services to you.

Certain links, including hypertext links, in our site, will take you outside our site. Links are provided for your convenience and inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement or approval by us of the linked site, its operator or its content. We are not responsible for the availability or content of any website outside our site and shall not be responsible for any transaction concerning goods or services available from such sites.

From time to time we may advertise competitions and/or prize giveaways on our Site. Prizes are supplied and distributed by third parties over whom we have no control and, therefore, we cannot accept any responsibility arising out of a third party’s supply or distribution of any such prizes.

Each of these exclusions or limitations shall be construed as a separate, and severable, provision of these Terms and Conditions.

## Variations

We reserve the right at any time without notice to revise the content of our Site and these terms and conditions. Any changes to these terms and conditions will be posted on our Site and by continuing to use our Site you agree to be bound by any such revised terms and conditions.

## Notices

Any notices you wish to send to us should be sent to us by email at [complaints@creativeboom.com](mailto:complaints@creativeboom.com) or by post at Creative Boom Limited, Third Floor, Canada House, 3 Chepstow Street, Manchester M1 5FW.

Any notices that we may wish to draw to your attention will be displayed on our Site.

## Enforceability

If any part of these Terms and Conditions is unenforceable (including any provision in which we exclude our liability to you) the enforceability of any other part of these Terms and Conditions will not be affected.

## Third party rights

Except for our affiliates, directors, employees or representatives, a person who is not a party to this agreement has no right under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999 to enforce any term of this agreement but this does not affect any right or remedy of a third party that exists or is available apart from under that Act.

## Governing law

These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with English law and the English courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction to resolve any disputes between us.

## Entire agreement

These Terms and Conditions, together with our privacy policy, set out the whole of our agreement and supersede any previous agreements, arrangements, undertakings or proposals.

## Privacy Policy

Creative Boom Limited (“Creative Boom”) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can let us know if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

By registering as a user and/ or by using our website, you are indicating that you have read this privacy policy and understand that your personal information may be used as described below.

If you have any comments or queries in connection with our privacy policy please contact us by email at [complaints@creativeboom.com](mailto:complaints@creativeboom.com) or write to us at Creative Boom Limited, Third Floor, Canada House, 3 Chepstow Street, Manchester M1 5FW.

## What we collect

We may collect personal information from our website and from other communications, such as emails. We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including mailing and email addresses and telephone and fax numbers
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences an interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * any other information you volunteer to provide to us
  * information that we receive or obtain from other sources
  * your domain name and IP address, operating system, browser, version and the website that you visited prior to our site. We may do this by way of a cookie (for more information about cookies see below). 

## What we do with the information we gather

When you provide information to us or we obtain information about you we will store this data and hold it on our computers or in hard copy form. 

We may use such information for the following purposes:

  * internal record keeping
  * to monitor and improve our website and any products and/or services we may provide
  * to send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting 
  * to contact you (by email, telephone, mail or otherwise) for market research purposes or to send surveys to you
  * to contact you (by email, telephone, mail or otherwise) in relation to any competitions we may run on our website
  * to customise the website according to your interests.

We may give information about you (on the understanding that such information will be kept confidential) to employees and agents (including third parties who distribute prizes for the competitions we run on our website) of Creative Boom. 

We may disclose information you provide to us or which we obtain about you:

  * to any law enforcement agency requesting it in connection with the commission of a criminal offence, if we are reasonably satisfied as to the circumstances surrounding the request
  * to comply with any applicable laws 
  * to protect other users of our website and ourselves

## How long do we keep this information?

We keep your information for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected The length of time we retain this information may also be determined by legal considerations - we are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfil our statutory obligations (e.g. for accounting/tax purposes). We review our retention periods on a regular basis.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you do not wish to receive promotional emails or surveys or be contacted for market research or prize distribution purposes you can opt-out by notifying us at any time by email at [complaints@creativeboom.com](mailto:complaints@creativeboom.com).

## Where We Store Your Personal Data

The data that we collect from you will usually be stored inside the UK or the European Economic Area (EEA). However, if you live or work outside of the UK or the EEA, we may need to transfer your personal data outside of the UK or the EEA to respond to any queries that you may have. Where this applies, we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy notice.

## Our Third Party Data Processors

We use several third parties to process personal data on our behalf. All processors acting on our behalf process your data in accordance with instructions from us and comply with this privacy notice, the relevant data protection laws and any other appropriate security measures:

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your computer's hard drive. Cookies let us know which pages are being viewed on our website and let us determine how frequently these pages are visited, we also gather information about the geographical location of our site visitors. This helps us improve our website and tailor it to our users' needs. We use Google Analytics for this purpose - which sends several cookies to your browser. If you would like to opt-out of data collection by Google Analytics, you can find out more information [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This will not prevent you from browsing the Creative Boom site but will prevent you from logging into your Creative Boom account.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. We are not responsible for the data policies or procedures or content of any linked websites. You should check the privacy policy of each website you visit.

## Sale of business

If our business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchaser’s advisers and will be passed on to any new owners of the business. 

## Security

We have put in place various security procedures to minimise the risk of unauthorised access or disclosure and to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, the internet is not a secure medium and we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose online. You accept the risks of providing information and dealing online over the internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless such breach is due to our negligence or wilful default.

## Your rights

You have certain rights with regards to the personal information we hold about you, including the following:

  * Right of access: you have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you
  * Right to rectification: you have the right to ask us to rectify information we hold about you which you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.
  * Right to erasure: You have the right to ask us to erase your personal information in certain circumstances
  * Right to restriction of processing: You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information in certain circumstances
  * Right to object to processing: You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on the basis of our legitimate interests
  * Right to portability: For personal information which you have supplied to us, you have the right to ask that we provide that information to you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format

## Exercising your rights

If you would like to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us at hello@creativeboom.com, or at the address above. We may need to request specific information from you to confirm your identity. You will not have to pay a fee to exercise the rights set out above, but we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is unfounded, repetitive or excessive.

We will try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In these cases, we will notify you and keep you informed about your request.

You also have the right to complain to the ICO - [www.ico.org.uk](https://www.ico.org.uk/) – if you feel there is a problem with the way we are handling your data.

## Changes to this policy

Any future changes to this policy will be posted on our website, and so we recommend that you occasionally revisit this page to review any updates. If we make significant changes we'll ensure that these are clearly pointed out on this website.

We keep this policy under regular review. It was last updated in May 2018.
